If you wanted to write tests for Django, know that you need to use a separate test case
class, not the one that comes in the standard library with Python, but instead use Django.test
test case, and there's guides for running Django tests right here in the course website.
And before we talk about the final, actually I'll give you an overview of the final project practice,
and then we will wrap up, and you will be done with a brain cramped full of Python knowledge.
For the final project practice, you're going to make sure that you're all set up, and then you're going to do a few things.
We're going to sort in reverse order.
So if you saw earlier our blog posts are in chronological order, which is not what we want.
We want them to sort in reverse so that the newest posts are first.
We're also going to add a new is draft fields so that we can have some posts that we're working on, but we don't want to display it.
And then we're also going to write or examine some unit tests.
And there's some links here for going further with Django.